Arjun TS

User Experience Designer

+91 8891355391 mail.arjunts@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/arjunts behance.net/arjunts arjun-ts.github.io

About Me

I am a multidisciplinary designer with a curious mind, I enjoy to meet new people and understand how they are solving problems, I invest my time to learn more about design (research, design thinking, design system, etc). An active follower of NPTEL, The Futur, The Flux Academy, Johny Vino, Alysha Naples, Andy Krik, Aaron Koblin.

Over +5 years, I've worked on a diverse set of projects, working from research to production, that includes iOS, Android, Web, SaaS, B2B, B2C, Data visualization, Augmented Reality, and Virtual Reality.

Experience

Spinach Studios. Mumbai Lead Visual Designer DEC 2020- TILL

Prudential Financial Leading the team of the visual designers for the markets

of Brazil, China and Singapore and reporting to VP Digital

products of Prudential.

Spinach Studios. Mumbai Sr. User Experience Designer DEC 2019- DEC 2020

Started as a Sr. Ux designer, most of my works were in Banking, Insurance, and Financial, and Edutech products. One of the Key achievements is designing the Design system for the Prudential. Also worked on projects for Plaksha University, Dr vaidya, Lead School, Zee Mobile App, Savvy Financials, TracePlus, SafeAir, and Reliance FPNP (CSR Project).

Prudential Financial Lead Visual Designer for the Sales Work Bench and assisting

the UX team in Sketches and Wireframes

HDFC Bank

Leading the Ux team, handling the client and provide Concepts,

Sketches, Wireframes, Prototype, and UI designs for HDFC Mobile

App and Cancer Insurance web app.

Tuna Software Solutions.Kochi Ui/Ux Designer AUG 2018- NOV 2019

Initiated & contributed to several projects involving web usability, Interaction, User interfaces, mobile augmented reality, and virtual reality. It was a leap in my career to learn and design for Kiosk, Virtual, and Augmented reality apps. My role was to design the interface and align it with clients from the USA, Mexico, etc.

Codegreen Technologies.Kochi Ui Designer Jan 2016- Aug 2018

The starting point of my career, learned a lot in designing, mostly in the role of UI designer but got a hand in Branding and Graphics design.

Arjun TS

User Experience Designer

+91 8891355391 mail.arjunts@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/arjunts behance.net/arjunts arjun-ts.github.io

Skills
User Experience Design

User research and Interviews • A/B Testing & Experiments • User persona and behaviour study • Information Architecture • Wire-framing and prototyping. •

Gamification. • Heuristic Evaluation. • Data Visualisation

User Interface Design

User Interface Design • Illustration • Typography • Accessibility • Colour Psychology •

Design System and Guidelines • UI Auditing • Mood-boards • Iconography

Interaction Design (Actively Learning)

Motion Design • Mental Models • HCI • Goal-Driven • Intrinsic Motivation

Tools Adobe XD Figma Keynote

Adobe Photoshop Sketch Milanote

Adobe Illustrator Blender Miro

Adobe After Effects Webflow Slack/Asana/Trello

Education IIT Madras BSc Data Science (2021-2023)

Ravindranath Tagore University B.A English (2016-2019)

MG University B.Tech Aeronautical Engineering (2011-2015)

MG University BSc Mathematics (2010-2011)